A Guide to the Tazewell family papers, 1623-1930
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Papers, 1623-1930
Library of Virginia
24194
6.435 cubic feet
Tazewell family
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Acc. 21619 was purchased from Martha R. Adams, Lynchburg, Virginia, 30 September 1939.
Acc. 21673 was purchased from Mrs. A. J. Davis, Richmond, Virginia, 1 February 1940.
Acc. 22066 was purchased from James Lewis Hook, Bala-Cynwyd, Pennsylvania, 22 July 1942.
Acc. 23749 was purchased from Mrs. C. W. Tazewell, Tampa, Florida, 19 November 1951.
Acc. 24194 was purchased from C. W. Tazewell, Tampa, Florida, 16 July 1954.
Acc. 24199 lent for copying by C. W. Tazewell, Tampa, Florida, 3 August 1954.
Acc. 24230 lent for copying by Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21 October 1954.
Acc. 27157 was a gift from Edmund Berkeley, Jr., acting curator at the University of Virginia library, Charlottesville, Virginia, June 30 1969.
Alternative Form
Also available on microfilm (Misc. reels 670-681).
Biographical Information
Henry Tazewell was born 27 November 1753 in Brunswick County, Virginia, to Littleton Tazewell and Mary Gray Tazewell. He attended the College of William and Mary, then studied law under his uncle John Tazewell in Williamsburg, Virginia. He represented Brunswick County and then Williamsburg in the House of Delegates from 1776 to 1786. Tazewell was appointed to the General Court in 1785, and served as chief justice from 1789 to 1793. He then was appointed judge of the Virginia Court of Appeals that year. The Virginia General Assembly appointed Tazewell United States Senator in 1794 and he served until his death in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 24 January 1799. He was buried at Christ Church in Philadelphia. Tazewell married Dorothea Elizabeth Waller (1754-1777), daugher of Benjamin Waller (1716-1786), 13 January 1774, and they had two children, Littleton Waller Tazewell and Sophia Ann Tazewell who married Benjamin Taliaferro (d. 1801) of Williamsburg.
Littleton Waller Tazewell was born in Williamsburg, Virginia, 17 December 1774 to Henry Tazewell and Dorothea Elizabeth Waller. Educated by his grandfather Benjamin Waller and George Wythe (1726-1806), Tazewell attended the College of William and Mary, graduating in 1791. He studied law under John Wickham (1763-1839) of Richmond, Virginia, and was admitted to the bar in 1796. Tazewell represented James City County in the House of Delegates from 1798 to 1800. That year, he was elected to the United States House of Representatives and served until 1801. In 1802, Tazewell relocated to Norfolk, Virginia, to continue his law practice. He represented Norfolk in the House of Delegates from 1804 to 1806 and in 1816. President James Monroe appointed Tazewell a commissioner to settle claims under the treaty in which Spain ceded Florida to the United States. In 1824, Tazewell was appointed to the United States Senate, and he served eight years before resigning 16 July 1832. He served as a member of the Virginia Constitutional Convention of 1829- 1830. Tazewell was elected governor of Virginia in 1834 and served until 1836, when he resigned. Tazewell returned to Norfolk where he spent most of his time running his plantations in Northampton County, Virginia. Tazewell died 6 May 1860 in Norfolk, and was buried at King's Creek plantation in Northampton County. He was reinterred at Elmwood Cemetery in Norfolk.
Littleton Waller Tazewell married Ann Stratton Nivison (1785-1859) 15 July 1802, and they had nine children: Louisa Nivison Tazewell (1804-1873), Henry Tazewell (1805-1828), John Nivison Tazewell (1807-1869), Sarah Tazewell (1809-1810), Sarah Ann "Sally" Tazewell (1812-1892), Littleton Waller Tazewell (1815-1848), Ann Elizabeth Tazewell (1817-1898), Mary Tazewell (1822-1886), Ella Waller Tazewell (1826-1885). Ann Elizabeth Tazewell married Edmund Bradford (1816-1889), Mary Tazewell married Matthew Page Waller (1823-1861), and Littleton Waller Tazewell married Sarah Elizabeth Walters (ca. 1821-1877).
Scope and Content Information
Papers, 1623-1930, of the Tazewell family of Williamsburg, Virginia, and Norfolk, Virginia, consisting of the personal and family papers, including account books, accounts, advertisements, agreements, bills of sale, clippings, commissions, correspondence, deeds, diaries, essays, genealogies, insurance policies, judicial records, legal papers, notes, receipts, speeches, tax records, and wills.
Series I: Papers, 1650-1890, contain the legal, political, business, and personal papers of the Tazewell family, mainly those of Henry Tazewell (1753-1799) and Littleton Waller Tazewell (1774-1860). Papers contain deeds from James City County, Northampton County and Norfolk, Virginia, as well as other counties; wills of members of the Tazewell family, and accounts of their plantations in James City County, Northampton County, and Princess Anne County, Virginia. Also includes the political correspondence of Henry Tazewell and Littleton Waller Tazewell, both of whom were senators from Virginia; Littleton Waller Tazewell also served as a congressman and as governor of Virginia. Also contains correspondence between John Nivison Tazewell (1807-1869) and Hugh Blair Grigsby (1806-1881) concerning the Virginia Constitutional Convention of 1829-1830. Papers also include the personal papers of Littleton Waller Tazewell's children, including correspondence from Ann Tazewell Bradford (1817-1898) regarding the confiscation by the federal government of Sandhills Plantation in Princess Anne County during the Civil War.
Series II: Undated papers, correspondence, legal papers, political essays, clippings, and miscellaneous papers. Contains political essays by and legal of Henry Tazewell; typescript copies of letters, 1782- 1825, from Thomas Jefferson to Henry and Littleton Waller Tazewell; undated legal, business, political, and personal correspondence of Littleton Waller Tazewell; legal papers of Littleton Waller Tazewell; estate papers of Benjamin Taliaferro; papers related to Littleton Waller Tazewell's plantations in Northampton County; correspondence of John Nivison of Norfolk, Virginia; deeds and other legal papers; obituaries of William T. Nivison and of Littleton Waller Tazewell; remarks on the death of Jefferson Davis; and newspaper clippings.
Series III: Diaries, Account Books, and Family Sketches, 1650-1930, contain a family sketch, 1823, written by Littleton Waller Tazewell; account books, 1820-1826, of Littleton Waller Tazewell; field notes for land grants in what became Northampton County from 1623 to 1629, made by Littleton Waller Tazewell in 1835; plantation books, 1836-1852, for King's Creek, Old Plantation, and New Quarter plantations in Northampton County; plantation books, 1829-1849, for Sandhills Plantation in Princess Anne County; diaries, 1847-1852, of John N. Tazewell; letterbook, 1829-1830, of John N. Tazewell; register, 1821-1854, of letters received by John N. Tazewell; household account book, 1836-1837, of Littleton Waller Tazewell; inscriptions from St. Paul's Church in Norfolk made by C. W. Tazewell; and typescripts of letters to Henry Tazewell and Littleton Waller Tazewell from Stephen Decatur, William B. Giles, Andrew Jackson, Thomas Jefferson, William Ludwell Lee, and Benjamin Watkins Leigh, among others.
Series IV: Political correspondence, 1794-1858, including letters, 1794-1798, from John Taylor to Henry Tazewell concerning national and Virginia politics, including the presidential election of 1796; letters, 1831-1834, from John Floyd to Littleton Waller Tazewell regarding national and Virginia politics, Andrew Jackson, and whether Tazewell will run for governor; letters, 1789-1830, from St. George Tucker, Henry St. George Tucker, and Beverley Tucker to Henry Tazewell and Littleton Waller Tazewell concerning national and Virginia politics; letters, 1841-1846, from Francis H. Smith to John N. Tazewell regarding the Virginia Military Institute; letters, 1832-1858, from John M. Patton to Littleton Waller Tazewell concerning national and Virginia politics and legal matters.
Series V: Wills, Legal Papers, Notes, and Correspondence, 1623-1890. Contains copies of land patents, 1623-1675, which became Littleton Waller Tazewell's holdings in Northampton County; wills, 1656-1890, of members of the Tazewell family; depositions, 1759, for a case in King George County, Virginia; deeds, 1790, in Norfolk County; letters, 1822-1823, from Littleton Waller Tazewell to his sons Henry and John Nivison Tazewell concerning their education.
Arrangement
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically within each series.
Organization
Organized into the following five series: Series I: Papers, 1623-1890. Series II: Undated Papers, Correspondence, Legal Papers, Essays, Clippings, and Miscellaneous Papers. Series III: Diaries, Account Books, Family Sketches, 1650-1930. Series IV: Political Correspondence, 1794-1858. Series V: Wills, Legal Papers, Correspondence, and notes, 1673-1890.
Miscellaneous microfilm reels correspond thusly: Misc. reel 670-Box 1, Folder 1; Misc. reel 671-Box 1, Folder 16; Misc. reel 672-Box 3, Folder 1; Misc. reel 673-Box 4, folder 4; Misc. reel 674-Box 5, Folder 7; Misc. reel 675-Box 6, Folder 11; Misc. reel 676-Box 7, Folder 11; Misc. reel 677-Box 8, Folder 10; Misc. reel 678-Box 9, Folder 13; Misc. reel 679-Box 10, Folder 11; Misc. reel 680-Box 11, Folder 7; Misc. reel 681-Box 12, Folder 11.
Contents List
- 27 March 1650 (Box 1, Folder 1 (Begin Misc. reel #670))
  receipt by Thomas Dimnor (Dinn ?) for survey for 1600 acres by Edmund Scarburge (or Scarbrough)-Northampton County
- 9 February 1659 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  survey 1000 acres in Northampton County for Thomas Dimnor (or variation) by Edmund Scarburge-Northampton County
- ca. 1666 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Survey--3700 acres in Northampton County for Argall Yeardly--located in oversize Box 14, folder 13
- 4 September 1678 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Deed for 40 acres in Northampton County from John Savage to Thomas Duparkes, both of Northampton County-recorded 7 September 1678; note 1 March 1682 concerning payment of tobacco from Savage's estate to Duparkes
- 23 December 1689 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Deed for 1000 acres in Rappahannock County from Thomas Short of Rappahannock County to John Newton of Westmoreland County-recorded 1 January 1689/90
- 7 October 1694 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  will, Hilary Stringer of Northampton County-recorded February 1695
- 9 August 1726 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  plat for 576 acres-county unknown
- 27 March 1729 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  judicial records-Westmoreland County-George Eskridge as guardian for William Newton, son of William Newton
- 23 July 1730 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Account and receipt, 23 July 1730, estate of Matthew Phripp to William Calvert-no county
- 1 November 1733 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Act for docking entail of certain tract of land in Northampton County and etc. and vesting the same in fee simple for Gertrude Harmanson--located in oversize box 14, folder 10
- 31 July 1734 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  judicial records-Westmoreland County-Benjamin Berryman as guardian for William Newton and Benjamin Newton, sons of William Newton
- 1740 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  quitrent payment for Benjamin Berryman on land belonging to William Newton-Westmoreland County
- 9 April 1741 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  plat for 413 acres-county unknown-John Ralls, surveyor
- 16 July 1743 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  deed, Absalom Hall to William Tazewell--located in oversize box 14, folder 8
- 18 July 1743 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  deed, Thomas Spady and wife to William Tazewell--located in oversize box 14, folder 8
- 1745 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  land grant, dated 26 May 1666, from Governor William Berkeley to Mihill Hughill and Thomas Short in Westmoreland County-copy made by Benjamin Waller for William Newton
- 1747 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  part of an account for William Randolph-one side contains a receipt to Pleasant Cocke for William Randolph from John S. Clark
- 11 November 1747 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  survey of pretentions of Capt. William Tazewell and Mrs. Elisha Stringer--located in oversize box 14, folder 8
- 4 April 1748 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  survey for William Tazewell and Elisha Stringer--located in oversize box 14, folder 10
- 7 May 1748 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  survey for William Tazewell and Esther Savage--located in oversize box 13, folder 1
- 1752 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  suit papers--William Tazewell vs. Esther Savage--2 items--located in oversize box 13, folder 2
- 12 April 1754 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  warrant from George Nicholas, clerk of the Dinwiddie County Court for Thomas Fluwellin and William Rives
- 14 March 1755 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  court record in suit of John Eppes and James Thweatt, tobacco inspector against Thomas Flewellin and William Rives-Dinwiddie County
- 14 March 1755 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  complaint by James Thweatt, tobacco inspector, against Thomas Flewellin and William Rives-Dinwiddie County
- 12 May 1755 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  deed from John Thruston of Gloucester County to William Freeman of Norfolk--located in oversize box 14, folder 6
- 23 April 1759 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  survey of a tract of land in Stafford County belonging to Charles Harding
- 20 September 1759 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  deposition of James Kitchen and Mary Kitchen about Richard Porch and land owned by Samuel Skinker
- 21 April 1760 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  (date recorded)--bond from James Carter of Williamsburg to John Tayloe of Richmond County
- 1762 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  n.d.-fragment of possible plat
- 29 June 1762 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  memo on property of Samuel Boush of Norfolk
- 1 October 1762 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  from Philip Ludwell Lee, Stratford Hall, Westmoreland County, to Robert Cary and Co., London, asking that the company make a payment to Malcome Hamilton and Co. and Robert Mitchell, merchant
- 10 September 1764 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  bill (i.o.u.) from Mordicai Cook of Gloucester County to William Short of Williamsburg
- 1765 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  survey of lands of John Tazewell and Nathaniel Savage by court order 22 October 1764--located in oversize box14, folder 13
- 1765 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  deeds for land in Brunswick County from Thomas Twitty to Peter Twitty, George Twitty, Thomas Twitty, Jr., and John Twitty--located in oversize box 13, folder 3
- 11 May 1765 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  deed for lands in York County from Francis and Elizabeth Willis of Gloucester County to William Nelson of York County
- 30 August 1765 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  suit papers--Accomack County--John Goodright vs. William Bradford--located in oversize box 13, folder 3
- 1766 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  account of William Black with Jeremiah Bowles
- 25 November 1766 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  statement of the tobacco of Jeremiah Bowles at Black's Ferry
- 2 March 1767 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  depositions by Thomas Spady, Ann Peterkin, and William Bishop concerning Elias Roberts living in the home now occupied by Walter Hyslop in Tazewell vs. Savage in General Court-case originated in Northampton (?)
- 26 March 1767 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  deposition of Robert Johnston in suit of Thomas Bankes vs. William Newton-Westmoreland County (?)
- 3 November 1767 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Williamsburg-bond from John Thompson, Jr. to Benjamin Waller and Thomas Everard
- 1768 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Dudley Whitaker-fees paid to Benjamin Waller, clerk, James City County Court
- April 1768 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  decree in West vs. Bonnywell-General Court
- July 1768 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  King George County Court-Thomas Skinker vs. William Newton-verdict for plaintiff
- 1769 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Bartholomew Dandridge-fees paid to Waller-James City County Court
- 18 August 1769 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Halifax Court-Anthony Irby vs Thomas Read-court papers
- 29 August 1769 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  letter, John Tazewell, Williamsburg, to Thomas Burke, Norfolk, concerning claims on a female slave and concerning a legal dispute between Burke and another person
- 3 November 1769 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  judgment by General Court in case of Timothy Trytitle vs Nathaniel Littleton Savage, both of Northampton County
- 1770 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  deed John Pool and wife to Peter Edwards--located in oversize box 14, folder 8
- 24 April 1770 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  court order, General Court, in John Doe vs. William Newton, after decease of Thomas Skinker concerning land in King George County
- 6 July 1770 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  bond from Samuel Calvert of Norfolk to Matthew Phripp
- 24 October 1770 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  will of Henry Applewhite of Isle of Wight County, proved in November 1770
- 12 December 1770 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  bill of exchange from Roger Dixon to John Backhouse, merchant in Liverpool
- 12 June 1771 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  note from Anthony Irby concerning his suit against Thomas Read
- 15 June 1771 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  receipt from Graves Daniel (?) for 450 pounds to tobacco from Charles Harding
- 27 August 1771 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Archibald Cary--invoice--located in oversize box 14, folder 10
- 28 December 1771 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  bill of exchange from Carter and French to Perkins, Buchanan, and Brown, merchants London
- 1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  bill of exchange from John Tazewell to John Breakill
- 22 January 1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  deed of trust between Isham Eppes and Gray Briggs, both of Dinwiddie County-recorded July 1772
- 4 July 1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Warner Washington of Frederick County probably to an English merchant to whom he owed money
- 13 August 1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  John Page to Captain James Esten-regretting that he will not be able to pay Esten total sum of what he owes-and wishing Esten good health and successful voyage
- 21 September 1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  receipt from William Boon to William Newton for quitrents paid
- 22 October 1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Account, Mrs. Campbell to John Thomas for cole [coal] and turkeys
- 28 October 1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Anthony Irby to George Wythe of Williamsburg stating that Irby's opponent in a lawsuit is interested in arbitration and asking for papers relating and also when their case might be heard
- 10 December 1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  account of Dr. Thomas Clayton with Phripp, Taylor and Co.
- 24 December 1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  letter from Walter Coles of Halifax County to John Fox of Gloucester County stating that he will not be hiring Fox's slaves for another year and is sending them back; also includes a pass for the two slaves, Robin and Isaac
- 1773 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Accounts of Thomas Charles, 1749-1773 and Edward Athawes, 1747-1758
- 18 March 1773 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  plat and survey of John Tazewell's lands in Northampton County--located in oversize box 14, folder 2
- 3 April 1773 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  William Newton--memorandum on land he owns
- 3 August 1773 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  receipt from Joshua Storrs to Hugh Walker for payment
- 15 November 1773 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  judgment in York County Court-Matthew Phripp vs. Augustine Moore and Anne Mennis, executors of Charles Mennis, dec.
- 1774-1775 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  account of Thomas Newton Senr. and Co. with Elbeck Ross and Co.
- 1774 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  settlement of account between William Fanning of Greensville County and (probably) Henry Tazewell of Brunswick County
- 25 March 1774 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  memorandum of agreement between John Thackner of Dinwiddie County and Thomas Stith of Brunswick County concerning the sale of land in Brunswick County from Thackner to Stith-note on back indicates that Stith made his final payment on the property in May 1784, note on back by Richard Brodder (?) executor for estate of Thacker
- 30 March 1774 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  receipt from John Combs to John Scott Harding for 1476 pounds of tobacco as part of cost of suit between Combs and Charles Harding
- April 1774 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  court order for Charles Harding to pay George Brodwell 584 pounds of tobacco because of Combs v Harding case
- April 1774 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  court order for Charles Harding to pay George Brodwell 1052 pounds of toabcco because of Combs v Harding case
- 5 September 1774 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  letter from Robert Carter Nicholas of Williamsburg to Henry Tazewell of Brunswick County, thanking him and the people of Brunswick for their contribution to the "association" and aid of Boston
- 14 December 1774 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  copy of 18 March 1773 survey and plat of lands belonging to John Tazewell in Northampton County--recorded in Northampton County Court--located in oversize box 14, folder 2
- 1775 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  indenture, directors of Town Point Company to mayor and council of Norfolk--located in oversize box 14, folder 10
- 24 August 1775 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  receipt from John Combs to John Scott Harding for 2 l 10 s
- 13 October 1775 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  account of estate of Christopher Calvert, deceased, with Phripp, Taylor, and Co. from 28 August 1772 to 13 October 1775-note payment in 1784
- 10 June 1776 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  advertisement by John Heath announcing that George Glascock, Sr., and George Glascock, Jr., broke into his home and removed a slave named Joe once the property of William Glascock, dec., also includes list of names who were to receive warrants and were involved in the action
- 25 October 1776 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  invoice to John Tazewell from James Honey and Richard Harrocks of Richard Harrocks and Co. for a coffin for Colonel Richard Bland-includes receipt, 25 November 1776 for payment by Tazewell
- 20 May 1777 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  promissory note from John Burwell for 27 l 10 s to John Edmondson
- 21 June 1777 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  bill of complaint in Northumberland County court by Chloe Glascock, John Hughlett, and John Heath stating that Joe had been hired out in Gloucester County-George Glascock went to Gloucester County court and received a warrant to take Joe-petitioners want to prevent Glascock from selling Joe-Joe is part of the dower of George Glascock's, (father of George Glascock) daughter married to James Heath
- 15 September 1777 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  court motion giving Thomas Scott administration of estate of Amy Eppes
- 11 May 1778 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  letter from Sir Peyton Skipwith of Mecklenburg County to Henry Tazewell concerning a debt owed Skipwith by William Jeter of Mecklenburg County and legal proceedings
- 10 June 1778 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  statement by Thomas Everard of Williamsburg informing the justices of New Kent County that Mary Dandridge is unable to travel to the courthouse and state that she agrees to the sale of property by her and her husband to Henry Tazewell
- 21 September 1778 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Mary Read to Dr. Earbic stating that she is willing to have their dispute arbitrated so that it can end
- 13 November 1778 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  will of William Drew, possibly of Williamsburg-also contains a note by Henry Tazewell that Drew's executors shouldn't have sold certain land-date is from Tazewell's legal opinion
- 19 December 1778 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  receipt from Thomas Jefferson to Henry Tazewell for money recovered from estate of John Randolph for Pannell and Jones-photocopy
- 1779 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Jedidiah Turner to Henry Tazewell concerning a suit
- 1779 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Account, John Robinson to Joseph Prentis of Williamsburg
- 19 March 1779 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  loan office certificate for $431 and 5/6th dollars money due from Benjamin Waller to Nathaniel Walthoes? legatees-signed by John Page, lt. governor
- 1 May 1779 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  letter from Theodorick Bland to Henry Tazewell advising Tazewell to find a wife--also announces that he hopes to visit Tazewell soon--also asks that he be taken in a move to buy wine for 1/3
- 16 July 1779 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  account of John Robinson with Curtis Patrick
- 29 August 1779 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Richard McKintosh to Henry Tazewell-concerning a case he'd spoken to Tazewell about and asking him to come down to handle it
- 21 September 1779 (Box 1, Folder 4)